Hi everyone, my self Abhinandan Upadhyay,
your health insurance expert, today I am going to
tell you in detail about the plans available in health insurance.
Now we have HDFC Ergo's Optima
Secure plan, Niva Upa's Resure
plan, Reliance Health Infinity plan,
Manipal Signal's
Lifetime Health plan, and Aditya Birla's
Active One Max plan.
All these plans that I am telling you are
very good and comprehensive plans. We
only suggest these plans to you according to your requirements, according to
your budget, according to
your area. If
you have any query
and are confused about which plan to take,
which company to take, then
you should definitely contact Happy to Help
Service. I am
giving you my number in the description.
Thank you.